[
    {
        "question": "What do you understand by HTML?",
        "option1": "HTML describes the structure of a webpage",
        "option2": "HTML is the standard markup language mainly used to create web pages",
        "option3": "HTML consists of a set of elements that helps the browser how to view the content",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is the father of HTML?",
        "option1": "Rasmus Lerdorf",
        "option2": "Tim Berners-Lee",
        "option3": "Brendan Eich",
        "option4": "Sergey Brin",
        "answer": "Tim Berners-Lee"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML stands for ___",
        "option1": "HyperText Markup Language",
        "option2": "HyperText Machine Language",
        "option3": "HyperText Marking Language",
        "option4": "HighText Marking Language",
        "answer": "HyperText Markup Language"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is used to read an HTML page and render it?",
        "option1": "Web server",
        "option2": "Web network",
        "option3": "Web browser",
        "option4": "Web matrix",
        "answer": "Web browser"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which tag is used for inserting the largest heading in HTML?",
        "option1": "head",
        "option2": "<h1>",
        "option3": "<h6>",
        "option4": "heading",
        "answer": "<h1>"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which is used to create Web Pages ?",
        "option1": "C++",
        "option2": "Java",
        "option3": "HTML",
        "option4": "JVM",
        "answer": "HTML"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML is a set of markup ___.",
        "option1": "tags",
        "option2": "sets",
        "option3": "attributes",
        "option4": "none of the above",
        "answer": "tags"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML tags are used to describe document ___.",
        "option1": "definition",
        "option2": "content",
        "option3": "language",
        "option4": "model",
        "answer": "content"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML program is saved using ___ extension.",
        "option1": ".htmn",
        "option2": ".html",
        "option3": ".htnl",
        "option4": ".htnl",
        "answer": ".html"
      },
      {
        "question": "HTML program can be read and rendered by ___.",
        "option1": "Compiler",
        "option2": "Server",
        "option3": "Web Browser",
        "option4": "Interpreter",
        "answer": "Web Browser"
      }
]